{
	"greeting": {
		"text": "Hello!"
	},
	"introduction" : {
		"text": "What would you like us to help you with?",
		"options" : ["Take AGOA Quiz", "Readiness Guides", "Export Categories", "Packaging/Labelling"],
		"payload": ["quiz", "guides", "categories", "pl"]
	},
	"quiz": {
	  "1": {
	    "question": "What product(s)/service(s) does/do your company offer?",
	    "choices": [
	      "Fast-selling consumer goods (e.g. food, drink, confectionery products)",
	      "Consumer durables (e.g. furniture, hi-fi, appliances)",
	      "Industrial consumables or durables (e.g. raw materials, components, machinery, etc.)",
	      "Services (e.g. financial, creative, training)"
	    ],
	    "answers": [3, 3, 3, 3],
	    "info": {
	      "text": "AGOA industry sectors",
	      "link": "https://agoa.info/toolkit/industry-sectors.html"
	    }
	  },
	  "2": {
	    "question": "How long are you in the business?",
	    "choices": [
	      "More then 15 years",
	      "Less then one year",
	      "Between one and three years",
	      "More then three years"
	    ],
	    "answers": [5, 0, 1, 3]
	  },
	  "3": {
	    "question": "Is the trend of sales an inquiries up or down",
	    "choices": ["Up", "Down", "About the same", "Don't know"],
	    "answers": [5, 0, 1, 0]
	  },
	  "4": {
	    "question": "How many sales offices, sales locations, or distribution points does your company have?",
	    "choices": [
	      "One or more domestic offices and at least one foreign office",
	      "One",
	      "Two",
	      "More then two"
	    ],
	    "answers": [5, 0, 1, 3]
	  },
	  "5": {
	    "question": "For what timeframe is your company’s business plan",
	    "choices": ["Six months", "One year", "Three years", "No business plan"],
	    "answers": [-30, 1, 4, -50]
	  },
	  "6": {
	    "question": "Have you exported before",
	    "choices": [
	      "Yes",
	      "No"
	    ],
	    "answers": [5, 0]
	  },
	  "7": {
	    "question": "How much time is your company going to dedicate to export planning",
	    "choices": [
	      "Considerable planning efforts (three to six months)",
	      "Some (one to two months)",
	      "Minimal (less than a month)",
	      "Don't know"
	    ],
	    "answers": [7, 1, -15, -15]
	  },
	  "8": {
	    "question": "How quickly does management expect export operations to become self-sustaining?",
	    "choices": [
	      "Three years",
	      "Immediately",
	      "Six months",
	      "Don't know"
	    ],
	    "answers": [-2, 1, 2, -0]
	  },
	  "9": {
	    "question": "Has your company's management allocated (or re-allocated) resources for the export effort?",
	    "choices": [
	      "Assigned extra personnel only",
	      "Allocated extra financial resources",
	      "Allocated both personnel and financial resources",
	      "No extra resources will be allocated"
	    ],
	    "answers": [2, 3, 5, 0]
	  },
	  "10": {
	    "question": "Which of the following U.S. market entry barriers have you researched?",
	    "choices": [
	      "Tariffs and non-tariff barriers",
	      "International standards",
	      "Product modification",
	      "All of the above"
	    ],
	    "answers": [0, 0, 0, 5]
	  },
	  "11": {
	    "question": "When you were setting the US price for your product/service, what did you take into account?",
	    "choices": [
	      "Costs only",
	      "Market demand and Costs only",
	      "Competition and Costs only",
	      "All of the above"
	    ],
	    "answers": [0, 0, 0, 5]
	  },
	  "12": {
	    "question": "Have you decided on your preferred methods of payment for your export quotations?",
	    "choices": [
	      "Yes",
	      "No"
	    ],
	    "answers": [2, 0]
	  },
	  "13": {
	    "question": "What does your U. S. market analyses include of the following?",
	    "choices": [
	      "Structure",
	      "Market share and size",
	      "None of the above",
	      "All of the above"
	    ],
	    "answers": [1, 1, 0, 5]
	  },
	  "14": {
	    "question": "Have you decided on what distribution channels will you use in the US?",
	    "choices": [
	      "Yes",
	      "No"
	    ],
	    "answers": [3, 0]
	  },
	  "15": {
	    "question": "Do you have a clear idea of the mix of promotional methods that will be used in the US",
	    "choices": [
	      "Yes",
	      "No"
	    ],
	    "answers": [3, 0]
	  },
	  "16": {
	    "question": "Do you have promotional materials in English language?",
	    "choices": [
	      "Yes",
	      "No"
	    ],
	    "answers": [5, 0]
	  },
	  "17": {
	    "question": "Do you have a website in English language?",
	    "choices": [
	      "Yes",
	      "No"
	    ],
	    "answers": [5, 0]
	  },
	  "18": {
	    "question": "With how many countries has business been conducted?",
	    "choices": [
	      "None",
	      "One",
	      "Between two and three",
	      "More then three"
	    ],
	    "answers": [0, 1, 2, 3]
	  },
	  "19": {
	    "question": "Have you already discussed exporting to the U.S. with other companies that are already experienced on the U.S. market?",
	    "choices": [
	      "Yes",
	      "No"
	    ],
	    "answers": [5, 0]
	  },
	  "20": {
	    "question": "Have you participated in international trade shows in the U.S.?",
	    "choices": [
	      "Never",
	      "Once as an attendee",
	      "Two and more as an attendee",
	      "More then once as an attendee & at least once as an exhibitor"
	    ],
	    "answers": [0, 1, 2, 5]
	  },
	  "21": {
	    "question": "How much international business experience does your staff have, either/both in theory and/or practice?",
	    "choices": [
	      "None",
	      "Moderate amount",
	      "Considerable amount",
	      "Don't know"
	    ],
	    "answers": [1, 2, 3, 0]
	  },
	  "22": {
	    "question": "Which of your company’s employees speak English?",
	    "choices": [
	      "Top management only",
	      "Middle management and A",
	      "Administrative staff and A and B",
	      "None of the above"
	    ],
	    "answers": [2, 3, 4, 0]
	  },
	  "23": {
	    "question": "Did your company succeeded in obtaining a bank loan in the last 10 years?",
	    "choices": [
	      "Yes",
	      "No",
	      "Don't know"
	    ],
	    "answers": [5, 0, 0]
	  },
	  "24": {
	    "question": "What method of payment do you consider the least secure?",
	    "choices": [
	      "Open account",
	      "Cash in advance",
	      "Letter of credit",
	      "Documentary collection"
	    ],
	    "answers": [5, 0, 0, 0]
	  },
	  "25": {
	    "question": "How is your company using e-mail communication method?",
	    "choices": [
	      "External communication only.",
	      "Internal communication only.",
	      "Both as internal & external communication method",
	      "Not used at all"
	    ],
	    "answers": [2, 2, 5, 0]
	  }
	}
}